Joseph W. Llewelyn

jwllewelyn@outlook.com 07538 902 033 Cardiff, Wales

Computing postgraduate and technical German speaker with experience in legal, customer service and construction industries. Solid foundation of skills in programming, software engineering and data analysis/visualisation. Strong verbal communicator and can demonstrate initiative and adaptability in a range of work.

EDUCATION

MSc Computing Sept 2022 - Oct 2023

Cardiff University

Cardiff, Wales

- Developed a neural network in MATLAB to assist with glaucoma treatment compliance
- Developed a full-stack web application using Flask, AJAX and MySQL. Explored Agile development
- Produced interactive visualisations from raw data using pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib and Plotly
- Programming fundamentals and Object-oriented programming in Python, Java and JS

LLB Law & German 2:1 2013 – 2017

Cardiff University

Cardiff, Wales

- Studied abroad at Universität Innsbruck in Austria, 2015-2016
- Dissertations in human rights and asylum law, Austrian national identity
- Awarded the prize in the 'Study Abroad' photography contest.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Outdoor construction projects

Oct. 2019 - Present

Self-employed

Cwmbran, Wales

- Results-focused: worked with dynamic timeframes and costing estimates, maintained positive relationships with customers throughout project delivery. Took personal responsibility for quality of final product.
- Initiative: Proactive in learning new skills. Developed practical problem-solving and risk management skills.
- Adaptability: transitioned into a new field and rapidly gained skills necessary to succeed. Completed projects
 while adhering to COVID-19 restrictions. Continued to work while completing postgraduate study.

Paralegal March – November 2018

Eversheds Sutherland LLP

Cardiff, Wales

- Attention to detail: processed legal documents and prepared trial dockets. Committed to high precision and adherence to confidentiality, contributed to the efficiency of the legal team.
- Communication and teamwork: worked closely with paralegal colleagues, legal professionals, IT and external clients. Helped to introduce new team members to existing projects.
- Interdisciplinary liaison: collaborated with IT to define my team's requirements for a new database. Conveyed technical concepts to legal specialists. Drafted letters to repatriate documents to private customers.

Customer service 2009-2018

Hospitality sector, various Wales, UK

8 years' experience providing positive customer service in public-facing environments including supervising a hotel bar, catering for weddings and many years part-time at a renowned Welsh restaurant.

SKILLS

Deep learning with MATLAB and TensorFlow. NumPy, pandas, Matplotlib. Flask, SQL (MySQL), Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, C#. Linux, Windows, Android, Git, Docker, Azure. Photoshop, Lightroom. Languages: German (proficient, technical), Spanish, French (intermediate), Welsh.